phpfox.pro 2012-11-09

# Privacy Policy - Phpfox.Pro - Phpfox Modules & Themes

This privacy statement applies to the website and all products and services offered by Phpfox.Pro.

#### Information We Collect

Phpfox.Pro maintains your pertinent personal information, provided at the time of registeration, on the premises. Your email and other information will not be disclosed, shared, or used for marketing purposes.

When you place an order online with us, we ask you for personal information (your name, email address, phone number, etc.). This information is used to record your ownership of a product license so that we can provide you with product download information and support. This information can be also used to inform you about an updated version of the product that you have purchased from us.

We do not collect or store any credit card information.

#### Information Usage

Just like most of any other web sites, our web server logs will collect standard information that includes your IP address, date/time stamp, clicks/visited page, referring/exit pages, your browser type, platform type, etc., which are used to analyze, diagnose, administer and to provide better service to you. We also use cookies to record user session information to facilitate and improve our service.

#### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your information if necessary to do so by law when it relates to actual or threatened illegal harmful conduct. We may also disclose your information to law enforcement officers or others when contents violates any kind of rights to protect and defend the property or rights of Phpfox.Pro, the users of its web site or the public.

#### Disclaimer of Privacy

This site contains links to other sites that may have different privacy policies. We expressly disclaim any and all liability for actions and policies of third parties.

#### Changes to this privacy statement

We may decide to change this Privacy Statement from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Phpfox.Pro reserves the rights to change policies contained in this document at any time for any reason and without notice.**
